esato.com 2006-11-10

# Privacy Statement

Privacy Statement for www.esato.com

**Esato.com** has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website: **www.esato.com**. 

**State Management**   
We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site. Your IP address is used to gather broad demographic information. 

Out site uses cookies to administer the display of advertising banners, and the discussion forum uses cookies to store the following information: the last time you visited the forums, your username, and a unique session ID number when you login. These cookies are stored on your browser. 

**Data Collection**   
Our site's discussion forum optionally requires users to give us contact information (like their name and email address) demograhic information. We use customer contact information from the registration form to send the user information about our company only if they have explicitly requested so. 

**External Links**   
This site contains links to other sites. **www.esato.com** is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. 

**Public Forums**   
This site makes chat rooms, forums, mailing lists, message boards, and/or news newsgroups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. 

**Security**   
This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. 

**Choice/Opt-Out**   
This site gives users the following options for removing their information from our database to not receive future communications or to no longer receive our service. 

**Correct/Update**   
This site gives users the following options for changing and modifying information previously provided. You can edit your account information here. 

**Contacting Esato**   
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact 

Esato.com webmaster@esato.com
